homehippo.com 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Homehippo.com

This privacy policy applies to all sites owned and operated by Home Hippo (Ireland) Ltd (‘the websites’) and includes important information for customers, users and all others (‘users’) who use, purchase, visit homehippo.com or any other site designed, hosted or managed by Home Hippo (Ireland) Ltd.

Please read this privacy policy carefully as your use of the websites implies your agreement to and acceptance of our [ _terms and conditions_  ](http://www.homehippo.com/footers/terms/)document of which this document forms an integral part.

This privacy policy is subject to change and users must ensure that they are aware of the latest changes published on this page.

 **The information Home Hippo collects**

Your contact details including but not limited to your name, email, address telephone number. These are saved for as long as you possess your user name and password. By providing your information and ticking that you agree for people to contact you on registration (this can be altered in your account details at any time) you agree to receive emails and sms from people who wish to contact you. The company Home Hippo (Ireland) Ltd is not responsible for the content of these messages and any subsequent contact you may have with people who contact you via this method.

\- Emails sent through the site are kept in accordance with the time period permitted by law.

 **SMS messages**  are sent through the website and the websites keep statistical data on SMS /text messages sent but not on the content of the messages. You cannot receive or send SMS messages until you register your phone, by registering your phone you agree to send and receive messages from the websites. You can un-register your mobile phone at any time by deleting it in the account page.

We collect and keep information on your navigation trail including patterns of usage, which pages you visit, advertisers you click on and copies of the electronic communication you have with them sent through our site.

 **Cookie information.  **We send a cookie to your computer which allows the site to identify your browser you are using for navigation of the internet. This contains a unique string of code which we use to remember your preferences such as the language and currency you wish to view the site in. These cookies are stored on your computer. To remove them go to your browser tools section and select to remove them. If you do remove the cookies please note that your user experience will be compromised.

 **Log information.**  As with most websites we operate log files on our server which record all accesses to the site. We log visits, entry and exit pages, IP addresses, cookies, browser language, and pages viewed. The cookies we send can uniquely identify your browser. Any user who is banned from the site in certain circumstances will also have their IP address banned from accessing the site.

 **Information we do not collect**

Electronic messenger communication such as skype, yahoo, msn etc chats are not recorded at all but as a publicly accessible website we cannot prevent people from contacting you in this way. To remove your electronic messenger information just delete it from your user account at any time.

 **How we use the information**

We use this information to enhance your user experience by providing relevant, personalized content as you navigate the site.

To send you newsletters that you have signed up for. You can opt out of your newsletters at any time by clicking the opt out link at the bottom or un-ticking the box of the newsletter you want to stop on your account page. We also track the click troughs, and read and delivery receipts for these newsletters.

We also use the information to perform statistical analysis of user trends and interests in order to target our marketing and to improve our content.

To notify you of important changes to the websites or new features and services as well as part of marketing campaigns and promotions run by the websites. You always have the choice to opt out of these at any time by clicking the opt out link at the bottom of every email.

To operate and run the websites and to ensure that they are offering content that users require.

We also aggregate statistics on user patterns such as page views, length of visit, number of visitors and advertising interest levels. This information we do share with third parties interested in working with us to provide them with the data they need to decide whether to work with us or not. We do not share information of individual users.

We reserve the right to disclose personal, browser, statistics and electronic communication and any other information necessary on individuals or users which we believe, in good faith, is necessary to enforce our terms and conditions. This includes providing this information to law enforcement agencies as required by law and to investigate, defend, or protect the interests of the websites or individual users of the websites in a court of law. We also reserve the right to disclose this information in any litigation arising from use of the websites and to prosecute any violation of our terms and conditions.

 **Third party advertisers**

All links to other sites and adverts on the websites may use technology to track interest in and effectiveness of their adverts. They may use javascript, cookies or other tracking technology to receive this information. Once you click through you are no longer subject to this privacy policy, please exercise caution when clicking through to a third party website. The Home Hippo websites collect statistical aggregate information on all click throughs on adverts and links posted on the site, each advertiser has access to this through their username. We do not provide any personal information of the people who click through.

 **Hacking**

We have employed every reasonable care to prevent malicious entry to our site, database or server. We employ many methods to avoid hacking attempts. We employ methods to protect your email address from hackers but if despite our best efforts you believe that you have witnessed an attempt to hack into the websites or you have received spam email you believe has been caused by Home Hippo please email [ _spam@homehippo.com_](mailto:spam@homehippo.com)  .

 **Internationalisation**

Home Hippo sites are hosted in Eire,  the UK and other datacenters worldwide.

If you are visiting and using any of our websites owned and operated by Home Hippo (Ireland) Ltd, even if this site is in another country with a country extension such as .es, .eu etc you agree that by accessing the site you transfer your information to Eire and you agree to be governed by Irish law, this privacy policy and the [ _terms and conditions_](http://www.homehippo.com/footers/terms/)  contained on this site.

 **Sale/Merger/Bankruptcy**

In the event that Home Hippo (Ireland) Ltd sells off or merges all or part of its business you agree to transfer your details to the acquiring party. In any circumstances where there is a change of control of the company you agree to transfer your information to the person(s), company or third party as part of such a merger, sale, change of control or acquisition.

In the case of bankruptcy, insolvency or other liquidation we cannot guarantee to be able to control how your personal information is transferred and used.
